Contact

curisce@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cristobalcuris (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Floor Plans

Site Visits

Problem Solving

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Critical Thinking

Fast Track to Digital Marketing

Cristobal C.

Experiential & Integrated Producer

New York, New York, United States

Summary

NYC-based integrated producer and creative projects manager with nearly a decade in agency and in-house experience.

Whether it's crafting custom branded content, bespoke IRL experiences, or global trade shows, my passion lies in transforming concepts into realities.

Let's connect!

Experience

Amplify

Producer

September 2023 - Present (1 year 6 months)

New York, New York, United States

DIZON INC.

Producer

June 2023 - October 2023 (5 months)

New York, New York, United States

Curate dynamic brand experiences, serving as primary client liaison.

Oversee sourcing and management of external talent and vendors, aligning with client budgets and expectations.

Happier

Sr. Manager, Production

January 2023 - April 2023 (4 months)

New York, New York, United States

Led event production for Water Street Associates building (WSA, opened in 2023), a modern 700,000 sq. ft. multi-use building in FiDi, as well as managed and ideated programming for 99 Scott

Executed successful transformation of unfinished WSA building site into premiere inaugural event–GQ's Global Creativivity Awards dinner & after-party – including oversight of event design and production as well as the creation and execution of construction & licensing timelines

Worked closely with cross-departmental teams (sales, design) to concept upcoming programming at both WSA and 99 Scott properties, serving as the main point of contact for all external partners (clients, production agencies, vendors)

Imprint Projects
Producer
July 2021 - December 2022 (1 year 6 months)
New York, New York, United States

Clients: Eventbrite, Levi's, Soundcloud, Stitch Fix, Smashbox, Pinterest, Twitter

Managed creative campaign development from end to end, inclusive of production timelines, and overall trafficking of deliverables in harmony with key stakeholders (design, finance, legal, and strategy) to ensure successful execution based on client KPIs

Collaborated with internal departments to create and present client-facing documents including proposals, production plans, presentations, and campaign wrap reports

Optimized, maintained, and oversaw campaign budgets to ensure maximum efficiencies for both agency and clients

Prepared call sheets, run of show, artist agreements, and contractor documents in line with industry and legal best practices

Served as key agency contact and manager of freelancers, collaborators, artists, and vendors

Informa Markets
Event Operations + Marketing
May 2019 - June 2021 (2 years 2 months)
New York, New York, United States

Events: MAGIC, Coterie, PROJECT, MICAM Americas, Children's Club

Managed operational work streams for multi-million dollar, fast paced B2B installations

Maintained costs and show budgets and reconciled with the Finance Dept. and external vendors

Leveraged Salesforce programming to create regular exhibitor reports

LUME studios
Event Producer + Venue Manager
June 2018 - April 2019 (11 months)
New York, New York, United States

Clients: OVO, Supreme, Puma, Aldo, StockX, Rostrum Records, School of Visual Arts, Gigi Hadid x Vogue Eyewear, Makeup Forever

Produced boutique brand events for portfolio of 30+ nationally and globally renowned clients

Supervised production crew throughout entire event cycle including scheduling, briefing, and execution of all client deliverables

Paleo f(x)
Events Producer
February 2018 - June 2018 (5 months)
Austin, Texas Area

Worked alongside founders to produce wellness conference of 100+ speakers

MFA Architecture Site Supervisor August 2016 - December 2017 (1 year 5 months) Secaucus, New Jersey, United States

Clients included: XPO Logistics, Hartz Mountain, Phosphorus Labs

Supervised large-scale renovation projects and regularly reported on performance to clients throughout the process, ultimately reducing spend and accelerating project completion

UNTITLED, ART 8 months
Onsite Manager | Untitled Miami Beach

November 2015 - December 2015 (2 months)

Brooklyn, New York, United States

Programming and Development May 2015 - December 2015 (8 months)

Brooklyn, New York, United States

Embassy of Uruguay in the USA Cultural Affairs & Programming September 2014 - December 2014 (4 months) Washington, District of Columbia, United States

Paul Kasmin Gallery Gallery Associate May 2014 - August 2014 (4 months) New York, New York, United States

Education

The George Washington University